This sample should provide the following functionality:
1.	Finds all the views in a project and displays the names in a dialog. The user can select several of the views and when OK is clicked a new sheet is generated that has all the selected views placed in it correctly sized, scaled and aligned.
2.	When the command is executed a dialog should appear that contains the following:
a)	A tree view represents all the views’ names.
b)	A list of all title blocks.
c)	An edit box for the sheet’s name. 
3.    All views should represent by category, not including schedules, sheets.
