<labs>
  <lab1-1>
    <para>Say hello some more!</para>

    <list type="bullet">
      <item>
        <description>Revit</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>The Revit SDK</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>Visual Studio</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>Revit API Introduction Labs</description>
      </item>
    </list>

    <para>
      The Revit API Introduction Labs are provided in two versions,
      as exercises for completing by filling in the missing portions yourself
      using the information from the SDK documentation and the lab instructions,
      and a solved version which you can use to peek into if you run into any
      difficulties.
    </para>

    <para>
      In this lab, we explore the development environment, and how to
      create a skeleton Revit add-in from scratch. We explore the transaction mode
      and regeneration option attributes, and the add-in manifest information defining
      the link between Revit and the external command. Also, how the external command
      can be hooked up with a custom user interface by an external application.
    </para>

    <para>
      Before working on this lab, ensure that you have located and had a first
      look at the following important Revit SDK documentation, which contains all
      the information required:
    </para>

    <list type="bullet">
      <item>
        <description>Getting Started with the Revit API.doc</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>Revit Platform API Changes and Additions.doc</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>Revit 2011 API Developer Guide.pdf</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>RevitAPI.chm</description>
      </item>
    </list>

    <para>
      To complete this lab, look at the developer guide in the Revit SDK, in the file
      Revit 2011 API Developer Guide.pdf, and work through the walkthroughs described in
      Chapter 2, especially 2.2 Hello World and 2.3 Ribbon Panel.
    </para>

    <para>They show how to:</para>

    <list type="bullet">
      <item>
        <description>Set up a new add-in project.</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>Add the Revit API references.</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>Edit the add-in source code.</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>Create an add-in manifest.</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>Load and debug the add-in.</description>
      </item>
      <item>
        <description>Create a custom ribbon panel.</description>
      </item>
    </list>

    <para>
      You can work through the walkthroughs from scatch as described
      in the developer guisde, or complete the missing code in the skeleton
      file provided by the Revit API introduction lab exercises.
    </para>

    <para>
      The client id for the add-in manifest can be generated using the
      Visual Studio GuidGen tool or the Guidizer provided by ADN.
    </para>

    <para>
      This lab can also be used to explore the TaskDialog class provided
      for Revit-style message boxes.
      For further examples of using the Revit API TaskDialog features, please
      also refer to the HelloRevit SDK sample.
    </para>
  </lab1-1>
</labs>
