This sample should provide the following functionality:
1.	Given a selection of walls that make a closed outline, generate a floor using that outline.
2.	When the command is executed a dialog should appear that contains the following:
a)	A drop down list box containing all the floor types.
b)	A check box show the floor to be created is structural or not.
c)	A preview window should display the closed outline. The graphics should be resized to fit the preview pane. No form or zooming, panning or rotating is required.
3.	There should be a warning for walls unclosed outline.